Guide to the Norton Nicholls Correspondence
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1750 Jun 27
  - Dawson Turner to Norton Nicholls. Yarmouth. Concerns literature, 1805 Jul 2 (Box 8, Folder 802)
  - J[oseph] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Goodmanstone. Concerns advowson; John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield, 1805 Jul 25 (Box 8, Folder 803)
  - R. Twining to Norton Nicholls. Norwich., 1805 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 804)
  - E. Hamilton to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Two drawings of friends included., [1806] May 8 (Box 8, Folder 805)
  - George Boston (Irby), Baron Boston to Norton Nicholls. Hudson Lodge., 1806 Aug 21 (Box 8, Folder 806)
  - George Cambridge to Norton Nicholls. Twickenham. Concerns family, 1806 Sep 6 (Box 8, Folder 807)
  - John Baker-Holroyd, Earl of Sheffield to Norton Nicholls. Sheffield Place. Concerns France; William Downes; Thomas James Mathias, 1806 Sep 15 (Box 8, Folder 808)
  - J. Sayers to Norton Nicholls. Norwich., 1807 Apr 14 (Box 8, Folder 809)
  - J. Sayers to Norton Nicholls. Norwich. Concerns literature, 1807 May 23 (Box 8, Folder 810)
  - Mary Hood to Norton Nicholls. Yarmouth. Concerns Thomas James Mathias; literature, 1807 Sep 21 (Box 8, Folder 811)
  - W[illiam] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Felbrigg., 1807 Nov 5 (Box 8, Folder 812)
  - W[illiam] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Felbrigg., 1807 Nov 9 (Box 8, Folder 813)
  - W[illiam] Windham to Norton Nicholls. Felbrig., 1807 Nov 11 (Box 8, Folder 814)
  - Mrs. Wheler to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns John Wheler; clergy, [1807] Dec 21 (Box 8, Folder 815)
  - Mrs. Anderson to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Cambridge University, 1808 Jan 3 (Box 8, Folder 816)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music; family, 1808 Mar 12 (Box 8, Folder 817)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music; literature; family, 1808 Mar 31 (Box 8, Folder 818)
  - Abbe Coulon to Norton Nicholls. Richmond., 1808 Apr 1 (Box 8, Folder 819)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music, 1808 Aug 29 (Box 8, Folder 820)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music; Thomas James Mathias, 1808 Sep 8 (Box 8, Folder 821)
  - George Boston (Irby), Baron Boston to Norton Nicholls. Burnham. Concerns family business, 1808 Sep 16 (Box 8, Folder 822)
  - Arthur Cooke to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns family, 1808 Oct 7 (Box 8, Folder 823)
  - C. Milner to Norton Nicholls. Dorking. Concerns France, [1808] Nov 20 (Box 8, Folder 824)
  - Norton Nicholls to C. Berners. Blundeston. Concerns advowson; Suffolk, 1808 Dec 4 (Box 8, Folder 825)
  - Frances Joes to Norton Nicholls. Cotton., 1809 Jan 3 (Box 8, Folder 826)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. Norwich. Concerns music; advowson; Thomas James Mathias, 1809 Mar 6 (Box 8, Folder 827)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns family, 1809 Apr 22 (Box 8, Folder 828)
  - Norton Nicholls to S. LeBlanc. Blundeston. Purchase of a life annuity, 1809 Jun 14 (Box 8, Folder 829)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music; literature, 1809 Jun 19 (Box 8, Folder 830)
  - Unidentified to Norton Nicholls. London. Reciept of life annuity, 1809 Jun 21 (Box 8, Folder 831)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns music, 1809 Jun 30 (Box 8, Folder 832)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1809 Jul 11 (Box 8, Folder 833)
  - Mary Gurdon to Norton Nicholls. Hadsock Priory. Concerns family, 1809 Jul 18 (Box 8, Folder 834)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns literature, 1809 Aug 1 (Box 8, Folder 835)
  - Miss S. A. Glover to Norton Nicholls. n.p. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1809 Aug 10 (Box 8, Folder 836)
  - Mary Gurdon to Norton Nicholls. Penrith., 1809 Aug 22 (Box 8, Folder 837)
  - Mary Gurdon to Norton Nicholls. Penrith., 1809 Aug 22 (Box 8, Folder 838)
  - Mary Gurdon to Norton Nicholls. Grundisburgh., 1809 Oct 13 (Box 8, Folder 839)
  - Henry Hoare & Co. to Norton Nicholls. London. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1809 Oct 21 (Box 8, Folder 840)
  - R. D. Sparrow to Norton Nicholls. Worthing., 1809 Oct 27 (Box 8, Folder 841)
  - Mrs. S. C. Anderson to Norton Nicholls. Worthing. Concerns John Wheler; Parliament; Napoleonic wars; music, 1809 Nov 9 (Box 8, Folder 842)
  - Catherine Floyer to unidentified. Welbeck. Concerns Norton Nicholls; response to word of his death, 1809 Nov 27 (Box 8, Folder 843)
  - John Deck to unidentified. Bury. Concerns purchase of Nicholls' library., 1809 Dec 10 (Box 8, Folder 844)
  - Thomas Crompton to George Boston (Irby), Baron Boston. n.p. Concerns Norton Nicholls; Suffolk, 1810 Apr 5 (Box 8, Folder 845)
  - Thomas Crompton to Charles de BTonstetten. London. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1810 Jun 8 (Box 8, Folder 846)
  - Thomas Crompton to Charles de Bonstetten. Cranworth. Concerns Norton Nicholls, 1810 Dec 25 (Box 8, Folder 847)
  - E. Crompton to Charles de Bonstetten. Cranworth. Concerns Norton Nicholls; French translation of 847, 1810 Dec 25 (Box 8, Folder 848)
  - Miscellaneous personal papers, 1753-1811, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 849)